Usage: notebooklm login [OPTIONS]

  Log in to NotebookLM via browser.

  Opens a browser window for Google login. After logging in, press ENTER in
  the terminal to save authentication.

  Note: Cannot be used when NOTEBOOKLM_AUTH_JSON is set (use file-based auth
  or unset the env var first).

Options:
  --storage PATH  Where to save storage_state.json (default:
                  $NOTEBOOKLM_HOME/storage_state.json)
  --help          Show this message and exit.
